Guide to the New York Florists' Club records, 1887-1993.
New York Florists' Club records, 1887-1993.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York Florists' Club records, 1887-1993.
4532
New York Florists' Club
11.3 cubic ft.
Minutes, correspondence, financial records, clippings, photographs, and club notices and newsletters
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes, correspondence, financial records, clippings, club notices and newsletters (1909-1987); minutes (1887-1901); photographs of banquets, etc. Subjects include shows, the Fellowship and Scholarship Committee, and other activities pertaining to floriculture.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes, correspondence, financial records, clippings, club notices and newsletters (1909-1987); minutes (1887-1901); photographs of banquets, etc. Subjects include shows, the Fellowship and Scholarship Committee, and other activities pertaining to floriculture.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York Florists' Club
Subjects:
Floriculture--Study and teaching.; Flower shows.; Flowers.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Minutes, 1887-1890 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 1891-1901 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
- Minutes, 1909-1913 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 1914-1917 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
- Minutes, 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1921-1923 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- Minutes, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
- Minutes, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
- Minutes, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Minutes, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
- Minutes, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
- Minutes, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Minutes, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
- Minutes, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
- Minutes, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
- Minutes, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Minutes, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 11-13)
- Minutes, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
- Minutes and Records, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Minutes and Records, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Minutes, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Minutes, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Minutes, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Minutes, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Minutes, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Minutes, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Minutes, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Minutes, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
- Minutes, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
- Minutes, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
- Minutes, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
- Minutes, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Minutes, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Minutes, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Minutes, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Minutes, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Minutes, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Minutes, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Minutes, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Minutes, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Minutes, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Minutes, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Minutes, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Minutes, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Minutes, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Minutes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Club Notices, 1925-1927 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Club Notices, 1928-1930 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Club Notices, 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Metropolitan Flower Growers Association, Inc., 1948-1951 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
- Club Notices, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Club Notices, 1964-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Club Notices, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
- Club Notices, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Club Notices, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Club Notices, 1975-1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Club Notices, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- 50th Anniversary, 1936-1938 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- World's Fair, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 15-16)
- 1950 International Flower Show, Grand Central Palace, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 17-18)
- Research Lab, 1947-1951 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Research Lab, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- International Flower Show, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- 5th Annual Flower Show, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 75th Anniversary, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- I Fellowships and Scholarships - reports of research articles, etc. from Club grants, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
- II Fellowships and Scholarships - reports of research articles, etc. from Club grants, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 6-9)
- Fellowships and Scholarships - awards, 1935-1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Fellowships and Scholarships - correspondence, etc., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11-14)
- Fellowships and Scholarships, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Fellowships and Scholarships, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16-19)
- 75th Anniversary, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
- Cornell University Floriculture Employee Management Program sponsored by New York Florists Club, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
- 1970 International Flower Show, Inc. since May 1970 seal, papers, etc. - trade space contracts, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- International Flower Show, Inc. contracts, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- International Flower Show, Inc. - second floor, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- International Flower Show, Inc. - Plant Societies (1st floor), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- International Flower Show, Inc. - exhibitors, first floor, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- International Flower Show, Inc., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
- Past Presidents Association (Box 8, Folder 13-17)
- T.A. Weston Memorial Fund (Box 8, Folder 18-21)
- World War II Service Men's Committee (Box 8, Folder 22-23)
- World War II Service Men's Committee (1), 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
- Century Club Committee - 100th Anniversary, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 5-9)
- Seal press: International Flower Show, Inc., 1942 (Box 10)
- Seal press: Metropolitan Flower Growers Association, Inc., 1948 (Box 10)
- Rubber stamp: Metropolitan Flower Growers Association, Inc. (Box 10)
- Certificate of Incorporation: Metropolitan Flower Growers Association, Inc., 1948 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Photograph: 45th Annual Dinner and Dance of the New York Florists' Club, March 22, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Photograph: Banquet of the Florist's Club, March 17, 1910 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Photograph: S.A.F. and O.H., Organization Meeting of Regional Unit, Hotel Pennsylvania, January 7, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Photograph: 58th Annual Dinner Dance, New York Florists Club, Hotel Pennsylvani, April 28, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Photograph: New York Florist Club Annual Outing, Rye New York, June 30, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 2)